This season the Syracuse
women's basketball team has been showing resilience
on the court So far
they've collected 12 wins and 18 losses
with an even 8 to 8 record at home
Leading the charges Georgia Woolley
the team's top scorer averaging 16 points per game
for a total of 463 points on the board
Kyra
would sets the tone with nearly seven rebounds a game
from beyond the arc
Sophie Burrows has been especially dangerous
shooting almost 40% from three to 65
makes out of 164 attempts
And in terms of playmaking
Dominique Camp has been the most reliable
boasting an impressive
the point to one assist due turn over ratio
The team has faced tough competition
with opponents averaging over 71 points per game
Still they've delivered some thrilling victories
including a nail biting 66 to 61 win over by Ami
and a huge 93 to 87 road win at Virginia Tech
which really proved their grit
If I had to describe this year's
Syracuse women's basketball team
in one word it would be resilient
No matter the challenge they continue to fight
making every game exciting to watch Duck go orange